Guide to the WCSU Office of University Publications & Design Records RG 7.3.2 RG 7.3.2
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Administration
  - General Outreach
    - Human Resources, circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Brochures
    - Faculty Services, 2000-2016 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Includes experts guide, adjunct faculty handbook
    - Student/Faculty Recognition Events, 1992-2012 (Box 2, Folder 11.1)
      Includes Fifth Faculty Research conference, Academic Ties, and 12th annual student leadership banquet
    - University Computing (IT&I), 2000s (Box 2, Folder 11.2)
      Includes University Computer brochure
    - Posters, etc, 1980s-2000s (Box OS 2, Folder 6)
      Includes basketball schedule, open house, co-op, violence in the workplace, graduate studies, get creative, 1980s cartoon poster, anniversary celebration calendar, and misc. events calendars
  - Publications and Design
    - Sample Brochures, 1982-1987 (Box OS 4, Folder Items 1-3)
      Mounted on board
    - Post Card Collection, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 38-39)
      Postcards sent by staff and received by the department and an origial watercolor on a card by Cora Shaughnessey.
    - Diane Golden Correspondence, 1981-1997 (Box 2, Folder 40-41)
      Includes correspondence regarding faculty portraits, registration book layout, brochure distribution, flyer creation, viewbook samples, programs, etc
    - Jim Cordent Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Includes correspondence with Diane Golden regarding the creation of a new viewbook
    - Awards, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Includes advertising awards for admissions newsletter and newspaper advertising series
    - Digital Mechanicals, 1999-2006 (Box 3a)
      Compact discs, arranged chronologically then loosely by academic, student or administrative oriention. Many of the file formats from proprietary applications and the file versions are obsolete. Formats inclucd Quark, Photoshop, Illustrator and MS Publisher.
    - Digital Mechanicals, 2007-2013 (Box 3b)
  - Student Affairs
    - Original Artwork and Mechanicals - Residents Life pocket folder, 1990s (Box OS 10, Folder 7)
    - Original Artwork and Mechanicals - Student Handbook, 1992-1993 (Box OS 10, Folder 8)
    - Original Artwork and Mechanicals - Dare to Learn, 1991 (Box OS 10, Folder 9)
    - Original Artwork and Mechanicals - Save a tree, 1980s (Box OS 10, Folder 10)
    - Original Artwork and Mechanicals - student employment handbook, 1991 (Box OS 10, Folder 11)
    - Mechanicals, Student Activities Fund, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Mechanicals, Programs and Services, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Includes mail services, Career Services, Reaching Out
    - Orientation, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Includes bulletin re: student services on campus
    - Campus Guides and General Student Information, 1990s-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Includes student center brochure, student employment handbook, self guided campus tours, and campus guides
    - Student Phone Directory, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Student Calendars, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Academic Advisement/Student Services, 1990s-2000s (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
      Includes fliers on Career Development, Cooperative Education. Health Services, Counseling Center, Advisement
    - Counseling Center Safe Zone Program packet, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Safe zone was a program to train students and provide safe places for LGBT students
    - Child Center, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Includes mechanicals, logos, mockups for brochures, schedules, fees, and a promotional folder
    - Child Center, Cabaret, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Includes fliers and programs for the child center annual Cabaret fundraiser
    - Housing/Residence Life, 1990s-2011 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
      Includes guides, brochures, pocket folders, and postcards regarding policies and facilities.
    - Food Services, shuttle and Student Center, 1980s-2000s (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Includes promotional brochure for student dining services, shuttle schedule, and general brochures regarding services at the Student Center.
    - SGA, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 26)
      One Brochure regarding the SGA's Legal Clinic
    - Public Safety/Police and Substance Abuse, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Financial Aid, 2000s (Box 2, Folder 28)
      General info and a brochure on the EZ-Pay program.
  - Centennial Celebration, 40533
    - Centennial Campaign, undated; 40539 (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Commemorative Plate, undated; 40538 (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Photographs (25-13 x 19 b/w and color), 2003; 40537 (Box OS 13, Folder 10)
      Digital prints of WCSU Archives and other WCSU photographs.
    - Program of Events, 9/14/02, 2002; 40536 (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Promotional, undated; 40535 (Box 4, Item 5)
    - T-Shirt, undated; 40534 (Box 4, Item 6)
- Photographs
  - Department Photographs, 40377
    Scope and Contents
    Photographs in this series were generally transferred to the WCSU Archives in 2003 and primarily cover the late 1990s.
    - Administration, 40526
      - Bernstein, Dr. Walter and Dr. Carol Hawkes, 3/98, 1998; 40532 (Box photo-1, Folder 1)
      - Buccini, Dr. Eugene, 1998; 40531 (Box photo-1, Folder 2)
      - Hawkes, Dr. Carol (see also: Bernstein), 1997-1998; 40530 (Box photo-1, Folder 3)
      - Hawkins, William, 1998; 40529 (Box photo-1, Folder 4)
      - Morton, Dr. Allen (News-Times photo), undated; 40528 (Box photo-1, Folder 5)
      - Roach, Dr. James, undated; 40527 (Box photo-1, Folder 6)
      - Smithsonian Partnership Signing, 2003; 55777 (Box photo-2, Folder 31)
        32 4x6 color
    - Ad Campaigns, 1998, 40524
      - Photographs of buildings and grounds, faculty and students, aerial view of Westside campus, Child Care Center ribbon cutting. Also includes: institutional, transfer, evening, and Ancell School of Business publication proofs., undated; 40525 (Box photo-1, Folder 7-9)
    - Athletics, 40511
      - Basketball vs. Rampo (b/w), undated; 40523 (Box photo-1, Folder 10-11)
      - Basketball vs. Westfield (b/w), 1991; 40522 (Box photo-1, Folder 12)
      - Football vs. Norwich (color), 1992; 40521 (Box photo-1, Folder 13-14)
      - Football (color), 10/25/94, 1994; 40520 (Box photo-1, Folder 15-16)
      - Rugby (color), 1992; 40519 (Box photo-1, Folder 17)
      - Rugby (b/w), 1992-1993; 40518 (Box photo-1, Folder 18)
      - Rugby (color), 1993; 40517 (Box photo-1, Folder 19)
      - Rugby (color), 10/25/94, 1994; 40516 (Box photo-1, Folder 20-24)
      - Rugby (color), 1994; 40515 (Box photo-1, Folder 25-26)
      - Rugby (color), undated; 40514 (Box photo-1, Folder 27-28)
      - Soccer (color), undated; 40513 (Box photo-1, Folder 29-30)
      - Women's Basketball: N-T Photos (color), undated; 40512 (Box photo-1, Folder 31)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 40491
      - Midtown: Alumni Hall (color), 1997; 40510 (Box photo-1, Folder 32)
      - Midtown: Campus Shots (color), 1998; 40509 (Box photo-1, Folder 33)
      - Midtown: Construction (color), 1997; 40508 (Box photo-1, Folder 34)
      - Midtown: Fairfield Hall and Rainy Day Campus Shots (color) 10/98, 1998; 40507 (Box photo-1, Folder 35)
      - Midtown: Fairfield Hall, Common Areas/Evening (color), 10/98, 1998; 40506 (Box photo-1, Folder 36)
      - Midtown: Fairfield Hall, Student Center, Computers (color), 10/98, 1998; 40505 (Box photo-1, Folder 37)
      - Midtown: Haas Library (b/w), 1996; 40504 (Box photo-1, Folder 38)
      - Midtown: Misc. Campus: Banners, Alumni Hall, Students (color), 1998; 40503 (Box photo-1, Folder 39-40)
      - Midtown: Misc. Campus: Banners/Music (color), 1998; 40502 (Box photo-1, Folder 41-42)
      - Midtown: Negatives-Midtown, (color), undated; 40501 (Box photo-1, Folder 43)
      - Midtown: News-Times Color Photos (midtown), undated; 40500 (Box photo-1, Folder 44)
      - Midtown: Parking Garage Ribbon Cutting Ceremony (color), 5/6/96, 1996; 40499 (Box photo-1, Folder 45)
      - Midtown: Student Center Dedication (interior/lunch/reception), 9/16/98, 1998; 40498 (Box photo-1, Folder 46-47)
      - Midtown: Student Center: Sketch (color: mounted/foam core), 1991; 40497 (Box photo-1, Folder 48)
      - Midtown: Student Center w & w/out students (color) summer 1998, 40496 (Box photo-1, Folder 49-50)
      - Westside:Classroom Building (color neg), undated; 40495 (Box photo-1, Folder 51)
      - Westside:Nature Walk (color negs), fall 1998, 40494 (Box photo-1, Folder 52)
      - Westside:Negatives (color), undated; 40493 (Box photo-1, Folder 53)
      - Westside:O'Neill Center (color), 1994; 40492 (Box photo-1, Folder 54)
    - Classroom Scenes, 40488
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 40490 (Box photo-1, Folder 55)
      - Physical Education, 9/98, 1998; 40489 (Box photo-1, Folder 56)
    - Commencement, 40485
      - Dr. Roach and unknown recipient, undated; 40487 (Box photo-1, Folder 57)
      - May 1996 (includes Parking Garage and midtown construction), 40486 (Box photo-1, Folder 58)
    - Events, 40481
      - Candlelight Vigil, Sigma Chi/MADD (color) 10/98, 1998; 40484 (Box photo-1, Folder 59)
      - Centennial Photographs (25-13 x 19 b/w and color), 1998; 40483 (Box photo-1, Folder 59)
      - Halloween: Child Care Center & Old Main (color), 10/30/98, 1998; 40482 (Box photo-1, Folder 60-61)
    - Faculty and Staff, 40409
      - Agosta, Letty, 1997; 40480 (Box photo-1, Folder 62)
      - Alberetti, Robert, 1998; 40479 (Box photo-1, Folder 63)
      - Alberetti, Robert (Bio photo), 1998; 40478 (Box photo-1, Folder 64)
      - Astrup, Dr. Margaret, 1997; 40477 (Box photo-1, Folder 65)
      - Benson, Dr. Ronald, 1997; 40476 (Box photo-1, Folder 66)
      - Boelke, Walter, 1998; 40475 (Box photo-1, Folder 67)
      - Caruso, Dr. John, 1998; 40474 (Box photo-1, Folder 68)
      - Cooper, Dr. John, 1996; 40473 (Box photo-1, Folder 69)
      - Cordy, Dr. Thomas, 1998; 40472 (Box photo-1, Folder 70)
      - Cordy, Dr. Thomas (Bio photo), 1998; 40471 (Box photo-1, Folder 71)
      - Daria, Dr. Marsha, 1996; 40470 (Box photo-1, Folder 72)
      - Daryle, Dennis, undated; 40469 (Box photo-1, Folder 73)
      - Dye, Dr. Frank, 1996; 40468 (Box photo-1, Folder 74)
      - Erlich, Dr. Michael, 1998; 40467 (Box photo-1, Folder 75)
      - Erlich, Dr. Michael (Bio photo), 1998; 40466 (Box photo-1, Folder 76)
      - Fischer, Dr. Marla, 1998; 40465 (Box photo-1, Folder 77)
      - Fischer, Dr. Marla (Bio photo), 1998; 40464 (Box photo-1, Folder 78)
      - Gable, Dr. Dan, 1998; 40463 (Box photo-1, Folder 79)
      - Gable, Dr. Dan (Bio photo), 1998; 40462 (Box photo-1, Folder 80)
      - Gallucci, Dr. Nicholas, undated; 40461 (Box photo-1, Folder 81)
      - Gallucci, Dr. Nicholas (Bio photo), undated; 40460 (Box photo-1, Folder 82)
      - Garcia, Alejandra, 1997; 40459 (Box photo-1, Folder 83)
      - Hagan, Dr. Edward, 1998; 40458 (Box photo-1, Folder 84)
      - Hagan, Dr. Edward (Bio photo), 1998; 40457 (Box photo-1, Folder 85)
      - Hall, Francine, 1998; 40456 (Box photo-1, Folder 86)
      - Hall, Francine (contact sheet & negs), 1998; 40455 (Box photo-1, Folder 87)
      - Halloran, Dr. Laurel, 1998; 40454 (Box photo-1, Folder 88)
      - Halloran, Dr. Laurel (Bio photo), 1998; 40453 (Box photo-1, Folder 89)
      - Hamer, Dr. Josephine, 1997; 40452 (Box photo-1, Folder 90)
      - Hickey-Williams, Dr. Catherine, 1998; 40451 (Box photo-1, Folder 91)
      - Hickey-Williams, Dr. Catherine (Bio photo), 1998; 40450 (Box photo-1, Folder 92)
      - Hines, Dr. Paul, undated; 40449 (Box photo-1, Folder 93)
      - Isaacs, Dr. Kevin, 1999; 40448 (Box photo-1, Folder 94)
      - Johnston, Kathy, 1998; 40447 (Box photo-1, Folder 95)
      - Johnston, Kathy (Bio photo), 1998; 40446 (Box photo-1, Folder 96)
      - Jordan, Dr. Kathleen, 1997; 40445 (Box photo-1, Folder 97)
      - Khoo, Dr. Rondall, 2000; 40444 (Box photo-1, Folder 98)
      - Khoo, Dr. Rondall (Bio photo), 2000; 40443 (Box photo-1, Folder 99)
      - Kreizinger, Dr. Jean, undated; 40442 (Box photo-1, Folder 100)
      - Kreizinger, Dr. Jean (Bio photo), undated; 40441 (Box photo-1, Folder 101)
      - Kuther, Dr. Tara, 1999; 40440 (Box photo-1, Folder 102)
      - Leopold, Dr. Jack, 2000; 40439 (Box photo-1, Folder 103)
      - Lyons, Dr. Peter, undated; 40438 (Box photo-1, Folder 104)
      - Maskell, Dr. Susan, 1997; 40437 (Box photo-1, Folder 105)
      - McArthur, Maud, 1998; 40436 (Box photo-1, Folder 106)
      - McArthur, Maud (Bio photo), 1998; 40435 (Box photo-1, Folder 107)
      - Owoye, Dr. Oluwole, 1997; 40434 (Box photo-1, Folder 108)
      - Philbrick, Dr. Thomas, 1997; 40433 (Box photo-1, Folder 109)
      - Raftery, Karen, 1997-1998; 40432 (Box photo-1, Folder 110)
      - Raftery, Karen (Bio photo), 1998; 40431 (Box photo-1, Folder 111)
      - Rajcula, Jody, 1998; 40430 (Box photo-1, Folder 112)
      - Roman, Dr. Eric, 1998; 40429 (Box photo-1, Folder 113)
      - Roman, Dr. Eric (Bio photo), 1998; 40428 (Box photo-1, Folder 114)
      - Rosenberg, Dr. Ellen, undated; 40427 (Box photo-1, Folder 115)
      - Saad, Dr. Abubaker, 1998-1999; 40426 (Box photo-1, Folder 116)
      - Saad, Dr. Abubaker (Bio photo), 1998; 40425 (Box photo-1, Folder 117)
      - Shaw, Dr. Darla, 1997; 40424 (Box photo-1, Folder 118)
      - Simon, Dr. Paul, 1998; 40423 (Box photo-1, Folder 119)
      - Steinberg, Marjorie, 1999; 40422 (Box photo-1, Folder 120)
      - Sullivan, Judy, 1999; 40421 (Box photo-1, Folder 121)
      - Walker, Dr. Kerry, 1997; 40420 (Box photo-1, Folder 122)
      - Walton, William (includes contact sheet), 1990; 40419 (Box photo-1, Folder 123)
      - Weinstein, Dr. Laurie, 1997; 40418 (Box photo-1, Folder 124)
      - Wells, Terry, 1998; 40417 (Box photo-1, Folder 125)
      - Wittemore, Dr. Robert, 1997; 40416 (Box photo-1, Folder 126)
      - Miscellaneous:Contact Sheet, undated; 40415 (Box photo-1, Folder 127)
      - Miscellaneous:Miscellaneous, undated; 40414 (Box photo-1, Folder 128)
      - Miscellaneous:Miscellaneous photos & negs, 1998; 40413 (Box photo-1, Folder 129)
      - Miscellaneous:Negatives b/w (unidentified), undated; 40412 (Box photo-1, Folder 130)
      - Miscellaneous:Negatives (b/w) (Cordy, Erlich, Goble, Galucci, Hagan, Halloran, Hickey-Williams, Kreizinger, Roman and unidentified), undated; 40411 (Box photo-1, Folder 131)
      - Miscellaneous:Negatives (color) (Fischer, Hamer, Raftrey, Shaw, alumni w/beanies and unidentified), undated; 40410 (Box photo-1, Folder 132)
    - Students, 40397
      - Around Campus, (midtown & westside), undated; 40408 (Box photo-2, Folder 1)
      - Books, Fresh Face Kids, Science Classes, 11/3/98, 1998; 40407 (Box photo-2, Folder 2)
      - Cool WCSU Kids (color), 3/98, 1998; 40406 (Box photo-2, Folder 3-10)
      - Havener, Stacy (for Annual Report), 8/98, 1998; 40405 (Box photo-2, Folder 11)
      - Kozig, Beth, undated; 40404 (Box photo-2, Folder 12)
      - Michner, Samantha (N-T photo), undated; 40403 (Box photo-2, Folder 13)
      - Plock, Corry (for Annual Report), 8/98, 1998; 40402 (Box photo-2, Folder 14)
      - Rodriguuez-Robinson, Rosie (color), 1997; 40401 (Box photo-2, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous b/w (unidentified), 1997-1998; 40400 (Box photo-2, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous color (unidentified), 6/98, 1998; 40399 (Box photo-2, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous b/w (unidentified), undated; 40398 (Box photo-2, Folder 18)
    - Visitors, 40394
      - Barreca, Dr. Regina, 10/23/97, 1997; 40396 (Box photo-2, Folder 19)
      - Goodall, Jane (color) 11/96, 1996; 40395 (Box photo-2, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 40385
      - Dance Lithos, undated; 40393 (Box photo-2, Folder 21)
      - Koryoe Photos (color), 1997-1998; 40392 (Box photo-2, Folder 22)
      - Megan's Photos (b/w), 1998; 40391 (Box photo-2, Folder 23-25)
      - Nate Ancell: N-T Photo, (color), undated; 40390 (Box photo-2, Folder 26)
      - Objects (color & b/w), 1997-1998; 40389 (Box photo-2, Folder 27)
      - Photos for Promos (Dan Goble/negatives), undated; 40388 (Box photo-2, Folder 28)
      - Texture Backgrounds (color) & one slide, 1980-1993; 40387 (Box photo-2, Folder 29)
      - MBA Ad, undated; 40386 (Box photo-2, Folder 30)
    - Slides, 40378
      - Building & Grounds, undated; 40384 (Box photo-3, Item 1)
      - Cool Kids Midtown, 1998; 40383 (Box photo-3, Item 2)
      - Megan's Slides, 3/98, 1998; 40382 (Box photo-3, Item 3)
      - Misc. Campus shots (incl. Westside & parking garage), 1990; 40381 (Box photo-3, Item 4)
      - Quinnell (students), 1982; 40380 (Box photo-3, Item 5)
      - The NAMES Project AIDS Memorial Quilt, May 1993, 40379 (Box photo-3, Item 6)
  - University Photographer's photo archive
    - Prints - Jan 1970-Jun 1999, 1970-1999 (Box psa_1)
      Contents: Student Center; Kevin Issac; Dr. Jiminez; Dan Goble; Midtown Renovations; Westside; SGA; Career Fair; Graduation; Computer Labs; Nature Center; Tech Center; Willy Wonka; Library Renovations; DHS Future Teachers; students, Daryl Dennis, Connie Wilds; art show; Campus Ministry (Mexico); Pinney Hall Dedication; Math Conference; Macbeth; Henry Lee; Job shadow; Jesse Jackson Jr.; Jane Goodall;ISEP; Patricia Ireland; Library staff; Construction (Westside and Midtown); Number of photo packages: 25
    - Prints - Jul 1999-Nov 1999 (Box psa_2)
      Contents: Midtown renovation; Renee Hill; Pete Rose; White Street Accident; Weathervane; Julius Baker; Orientation; Cupola; Alumni; Homecoming; Westcafe; Basketball; Funny Girl; Century Gala; Midtown sculpture; Football;; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Dec 1999-Apr 2000, 1999-2000 (Box psa_3)
      Contents: Jason Cassel; Leo Nunes; Snow; Christmas Billboards; Mall; CTA Christmas Show; Nursing students; Midtown; Jack Leopold; Weight room; NCAA Div III; Yes Program; Westside; Career Fair; George Mitchell; Robert Pressler; Stop the Violence Day; Midtown shots; Jazz fest; Earth Day; Softball; Mitch Wagener;; Number of photo packages: 46
    - Prints - May 2000 (Box psa_4)
      Contents: Graduation; Spring Weekend; Westfest; Art Forum; Midtown;; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Jun 2000-Aug 2000 (Box psa_5)
      Contents: R. Gerber; Pinney conference; John Briggs; Music Camp; Concap; Stan Bazan; Library; Aram Govardran; Observatory; Number of photo packages: 24
    - Prints - Aug 2000-Sep 2000 (Box psa_6)
      Contents: Westside; Athletic Hall of Fame; Grad Office; Haas Roof; Ruth Gyre; Faculty BBQ; Orientation; Club Fair; Admissions; CL&P; Midtown; Football; Volleyball; Haas Library; Candlewood; Ives Center;; Number of photo packages: 21
    - Prints - Sep 2000-Oct 2000 (Box psa_7)
      Contents: Football; Soccer; Master classes; PE; Waterbury; Library interior; Hirshfield; Women's Tennis; Ives Nature Preserve; Cabaret; LIbrary Dedication; Emeritus Luncheon;; Number of photo packages: 23
    - Prints - Oct 2000-Dec 2000 (Box psa_8)
      Contents: Women's basketball; flute choir; dorms; Haas Library interior; Amahl and the Night Visitors (Opera); Dr. Montague; Community forum; Mel Bernstein; Hate Crimes; Football; Volleyball; Swimming; Wine tasting; WestConn Society; Tech Center; Future Teachers; Homecoming; Midtown; Men's Basketball; Number of photo packages: 23
    - Prints - Jan 2001-Mar 2001 (Box psa_9)
      Contents: Midtown Snow; John Wallace; Father Michael; Shuttle bus; Westside; Midtown; Snowstorm; student center; Old buildings for hot L Baltimore; Carnival; Joan Borysenko; Haas Library; New Hope women's choir; Ghana; Stop Gun Violence; Bill Smilovich; Faculty Art Show; Music Dept.; Lois Dodd; St. Patrick's Day; Yes Clinic; basketball; Number of photo packages: 28
    - Prints - Mar 2001 (Box psa_10)
      Contents: DPS; Warner Hall; JazzFest; Gate Installation; Violence against Women t-shirts; Alumni Circle; earth Day; Fashion Show; Dry Campus Forum; Amy Birch-Barnard; Kids on Campus; Women's Lacrosse; Career Fair; Baseball; Softball; Paul Simon; Athletic Hall of Fame; Executive Forum; Foundation Dinner; Student Leadership Banquet; President's Lecture; Radio 104; Margaret Leahy; Master Dance class; Dr. Philbrick; Computer conference; Dr. Wagner (german lecture); painting portfolio class; student social work conference westside nature preserve; Number of photo packages: 30
    - Prints - May 2001-Jun 2001 (Box psa_11)
      Contents: Graphic Portfolio Show; Midtown; Alumni Art Forum; Symphonic Smith/Jimenez; Stuart Little; Spring Carnival; University Awards; University Ball; WestFest; West Cafe; Pie Eating contest; Student Center; Peter Marcus; Haas night shots; German students; alumni picnic; GE Capital; John Rowland; graduation; Number of photo packages: 25
    - Prints - Jun 2001-Aug 2001 (Box psa_12)
      Contents: John Rowland; Irish Tenors; Shalamazoo; ConCap; Midtown; Music Camp; Computer Lab; MDA; Shuttle Bus; Library interior; Mayor boughton; Rich Sullivan; Richard Gerber; Gene Buccini; Pinney Hall; James Roach; Student Center; Deans; John Briggs; Walter Bernstein; Number of photo packages: 24
    - Prints - Aug 2001-Sep 2001 (Box psa_13)
      Contents: James Roach; Picnic for faculty; Weatherman Ron Weglarz; night shots of Haas library with people in them; orientation; campus shots (both campuses); social work dept.; volley ball; football; library archives; Marie Wright; community service; hope chest; Laura Pappano; women's tennis; Lionel Bascom; Nature Preserve; Pinney Hall; Admissions Staff; peace service; Irish Festival; patriotism; meningitis clinic; Newman dinner; Marie Wright; Number of photo packages: 21
    - Prints - Sep 2001-Oct 2001 (Box psa_14)
      Contents: Admissions staff; Kid's night out; football; community service; hope chest; football; Pinney Hall; music dept. sing along; Lionel Bascom; Laura Pappano; Mike Driscoll; Brass Quintet; Holistic Health Fair; board of trustees; sigma chi; FMA in illustration; women's soccer; volunteer fair; snack bar; cabaret; Dr. Matchell bagpipes;; Number of photo packages: 25
    - Prints - Oct 2001 (Box psa_15)
      Contents: Homecoming; Athletic Hall of Fame; Westside clock; homecoming queen and king; homecoming parade; westconn authors; homecoming street fair; Anything Goes; Hayfever Dr.; Number of photo packages: 16
    - Prints - Oct 2001 (Box psa_16)
      Contents: R. Blum; Pat Lund; Danbury Hospital; Rob Whittemore; Nectop; Brass at Library; Education club conference; Jerell; Ethan Allen Foundation; Tribute to Robert Watts; Men's soccer; Anything Goes; Flute Hands; Students in Haas Library; group marketing; Number of photo packages: 18
    - Prints - Oct 2001-Nov 2001 (Box psa_17)
      Contents: Halloween; Japanese Music; keyboards; new faculty; chemistry students; wine tasting; election night; vincent arcilesa; Number of photo packages: 17
    - Prints - Nov 2001-Dec 2001 (Box psa_18)
      Contents: Stew Leonard Jr.; blood drive; salute to veterans; claire geddes; Haas Library; Westside sculpture; Peter Lundberg; football; concert choir; nature preserve; emeritus lunch; meg moughan; SW response to 9/11; holiday cruise; miss brazil; computer technology; women's basketball; Dr. Luther Christman; percussion concert; executive forum; Ellen Pearson; holiday jazz rehearsal; group marketing; Terry Wells; Number of photo packages: 24
    - Prints - Dec 2001-Feb 2002, 20012002 (Box psa_19)
      Contents: Ives Rec. ceremony; yoga; Westside at night; Darla Shaw: Danbury commons; Ms. Brasil; James Roach; Women's basketball; Men's basketball; swim practice; weight room; tarrywile mansion; student center; Mark Boughton; snow shots; Shane Murphy; Kevin Hicky; Carol Hawkes; The Silo New Milford; Tom Dulach-Haas Library; Judith Riley Quilts; firefighters; winter warm-up; Number of photo packages: 26
    - Prints - Feb 2002-Mar 2002 (Box psa_20)